Guide to the Stanford University, Capital Planning and Management, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Housing - Project Approval 12/1986 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Housing - Articles (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Housing - Budget (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Housing - Building Cost Containment (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Housing - Constituencies (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Housing - Common Space (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Housing - New Undergraduate Housing Communication Plan (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Housing - HSGS Concept and Site approval (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Housing - Deal Dallas Trip (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Housing - Deli Program (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Housing - Rosse Correspondence (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Housing - Escondido Plots (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Housing - Facilities Reserve (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Housing - Fire Alarms (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Housing - Site Expansion Letters (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Housing - Monthly Status Reports (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Housing - Newsletter (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Housing - Outdoor Art (Box 62, Folder 35)
- Housing - Physical Program (Box 62, Folder 36)
- Housing - HSGS Report 1987 (Box 62, Folder 37)
- Housing - Program Advisory Committee (Box 62, Folder 38)
- Housing - Rosse/Massey Correspondence re. Gas, Electricity (Box 62, Folder 39)
- Housing - Parking (Box 62, Folder 40)
- Housing - Schematic Design (Box 62, Folder 41)
- Housing - Relocation Escondido Shops (Box 62, Folder 42)
- Housing - Staff Apartments (Box 62, Folder 43)
- Housing - UCLBD Discussion (Box 62, Folder 44)
- Housing - Land Lease Policy 1982 (Box 62, Folder 45)
- Housing - BOT Committee on Investments Real Estate Subcommittee 1981 (Box 62, Folder 46)
- Shared Appreciation Mortgages SSAM 1981 (Box 62, Folder 47)
- Stanford West Project Description (Box 62, Folder 48)
- Stanford West Project Forum (Box 62, Folder 49)
- Equity Sharing Background (Box 62, Folder 50)
- Mortgage Loan Policies 1978 (Box 62, Folder 51)
- Mortgage Loan Program Policy (Box 62, Folder 42)
- Faculty/Staff Housing Subcommittee (Box 62, Folder 43)
- Dean's Committee on Housing 1981 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Housing Coordination Meetings 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Task Force on COIN Program 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Peter Coutts Subgroup Committee (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Faculty/Staff Recruitment Problems 1976-1977 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Faculty/Staff Housing Study 1977 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Second Mortgage Guidelines COIN (Coinvest) Program I and II (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Housing Allowance Program 1982 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Housing Allowance Program Eligibility Policy (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Housing Study Research/Background (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Coutts Development 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Coutts Articles (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Coutts Survey Demand (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Housing Coordination Meetings 1981-1984 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Housing Program Report BOT 1982 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Factbook on SU Housing 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Budget 1985-1991 - ACIS (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Admissions (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Business and Finance (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Budget 1985-1991 - OandM (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Budget 1985-1991 - DAPER (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Dean of Student Affairs (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Development (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Earth Science (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Education (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Engineering (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Budget 1985-1991 - General Counsel (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Graduate Studies (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Budget 1985-1991 - GSB (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Hoover Institute (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Humanities Center (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Independent Labs (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Information Resources (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Information Technology Services (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Law School (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Libraries 1987-1991 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Libraries 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Medical School (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Memorial Chapel (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Overseas Studies (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Planning and Management (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Budget 1985-1991 - President/Provost's Office (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Budget 1985-1991 - University Press (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Public Affairs (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Registrar (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Research (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Budget 1985-1991 - SLAC (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Special Houses (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Summer Session (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Budget 1985-1991 - University Counsel (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Budget 1985-1991 - Western Culture Program (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Budget - BOT Ad Hoc Budget Committee Meetings 1975 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Budget - Allocation by Formula General 1975 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Budget - Allocation by Formula GSB (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Budget - A-21 OMB Circular 1979-1981 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Budget - Allocation by Formula Medicine ABF Discussion 1973-1977 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Budget - Allocation by Formula Medicine 1973-1977 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Budget - Medical Center University Financial Paper 1981 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Budget - Budget Group Agendas 1977-1979 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Budget - Budget Making 1978-1980 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Budget - Automation 1980 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Budget - Available Funds 1978 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Budget - Capital Budgeting (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Budget - Cost Sharing 1978 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Budget - Debt Capacity (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Budget - Endowment Concepts and Calculations 1978 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Budget - Faculty/Staff Housing 1979 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Budget - History 1949-1975 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Budget - Investment Performance (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Budget - Parameters Papers (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Budget - LRF 1977-1979 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Budget - Restricted Funds 1977 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Budget - Service Center 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Budget - Social Security Proposal (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Budget - Staff Benefits 1966-1982 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Budget - Faculty Club 1979-1982 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Budget - Taxes 1978 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Budget - Budget Process 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- Budget - Operating Budget Reconciliations 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Budget - BPC Meeting 2/15/1979 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Budget - Continuing Studies - Consolidated Income and Expenses 1977 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Budget - Task Force VI 1977 (Box 66, Folder 26)
- Budget - LRF Economic Context (Box 66, Folder 27)
- Budget - Reports and Papers (Box 66, Folder 28)
- Budget - Medical Center Ad Hoc Committee (Box 66, Folder 29)
- Budget - Medical Center Budget Advisory Group 1979 (Box 66, Folder 30)
- Budget - Faculty Practice Plan (Box 66, Folder 31)
- Budget - Fundraising Priorities Committee (Box 66, Folder 32)
- Budget - General 1977-1980 (Box 66, Folder 33)
- Budget - Medical School (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Budget - Personnel Decentralization (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Budget - Salary Relationships (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Budget - Stanford Hospital (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Budget - Budget Estimates and Background 1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Budget - BOT Committee on Medical Center Meeting 8/1986 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Budget - VA Pension Parity (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Budget 1980-1982 - Operating Budget Guidelines- Faculty Salaries (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Budget 1980-1982 - Parameters Papers (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Budget 1980-1982 - General (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Budget 1980-1982 - Migration analysis (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Budget 1980-1982 - Distribution (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Budget 1980-1982 - Faculty Salaries (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Budget 1980-1982 - Migration analysis (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Distribution (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Available Funds Summary (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Charge Out Rates (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Faculty Salaries (Box 67, Folder 18)
- Budget 1979-1980 - General (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Medicine (Box 67, Folder 20)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Migration Analysis (Box 67, Folder 21)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Parameters Papers (Box 67, Folder 22)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Staff Benefits (Box 67, Folder 23)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Status Report (Box 67, Folder 24)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Plant Transfers (Box 67, Folder 25)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Worksheets (Box 67, Folder 26)
- Budget 1979-1980 - Working Papers (Box 67, Folder 27)
- Budget 1978-1979 - Distribution (Box 67, Folder 28)
- Budget 1978-1979 - General (Box 67, Folder 29)
- Budget 1978-1979 - Endowment Income Estimates (Box 67, Folder 30)
- Budget 1978-1979 - Migration analysis (Box 67, Folder 31)
- Budget 1978-1979 - Parameters Papers (Box 67, Folder 32)
- Budget 1978-1979 - Plant and Buildings (Box 67, Folder 33)
- Budget 1978-1979 - Tuition Income Estimates (Box 67, Folder 34)
- Budget 1978-1979 - Working Papers (Box 67, Folder 35)
- Budget 1977-1978- Decentralization (Box 67, Folder 36)
- Budget 1977-1978- Conditional Budget (Box 67, Folder 37)
- Budget 1977-1978- Faculty Salaries (Box 67, Folder 38)
- Budget 1977-1978- Final working Papers (Box 67, Folder 39)
- Budget 1977-1978- Guidelines (Box 67, Folder 40)
- Budget 1977-1978- Restricted Funds Report (Box 67, Folder 41)
- Budget 1977-1978- Staff Benefits (Box 67, Folder 42)
- Budget 1977-1978- Working Papers (Box 67, Folder 43)
- Budget Presentations BOT 1977 (Box 67, Folder 44)
- Budget Presentations OBG Board 1976-1979 (Box 67, Folder 45)
- Budget Protocols 1977-1981 (Box 67, Folder 46)
- Budget Publicity 1970-1976 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Budget - Reports and Papers 1973-1977 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Budget - Academic Planning Office (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Budget - Funds Pending Reports 1972-1975 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Budget - Living Trusts (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Budget - Earthquake calculations 1974 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Budget - Parameters Papers 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Budget - Planning (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Budget - Sponsored Projects Reports 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Budget - Room and Board Rates 1970-1978 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Budget - Faculty Salaries 1976-1979 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Budget - Staff Salaries 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Budget - SRI Separation Payments 1980 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- [Tuition files removed by Legal Office] (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Budget - University Budget Priorities Advisory Committee (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Budget - Wage/Price Guidelines 1979-1981 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Budget - Year End Closing 1978-1981 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Subcommittee on Parking and Transportation 1970-1971 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- CPT (University Committee on Parking and Transportation) 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- CPT 1976-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- SU Regulations on Parking and Transportation 1975-1982 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Budget - LRF 1973 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Budget - Long Range Financial Program 1965-1971 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Budget - 10 year LRF - Financial Needs Background Data, Discussion 1969 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Budget - 5 year LRF - Tuition and Fees Income 1973 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Budget - 5 year LRF - Major Facilities Program 1969 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Budget - History of Schools, Etc. 1960-1964 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Budget - Salary Ranges 1957-1964 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Budget - LRFs 1981-1985 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Faculty Information on Age and Minority 1974-1982 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- BOT Investment and Planning Subcommittee 1983 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Budget - Allocation by Formula - Medical School 1974-1985 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Bacchetti - Encina Sit-In 5/1/1969 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Bacchetti - Campus Policy - Illegal Use of Drugs 1967 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Bacchetti - Strike and Demonstrations, Etc. 5/1970 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Bacchetti - Applied Electronics Lab Sit-in 4/15/1969 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Bacchetti - BSU Stanford Daily, week of 4/8/1968 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Bacchetti - BSU 4/1968 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Bacchetti - Old Union Sit-In 5/6-8/1968 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Bacchetti - David Starr Jordan Prize 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Bacchetti - Organizing and Planning the Budget Staff and Budget Process 1981 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Bacchetti - Financial Aids 1988 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Bacchetti - Statistical Reports on the Composition of Faculty 1981-1982 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Bacchetti - Financing Barchas History of Science Collection 1981-1985 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- El Centro Chicano 1980-1986 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- El Centro Chicano 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- El Centro Chicano 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- El Centro Chicano 1989-1990 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- El Centro Chicano - Budget and Planning Committee 1988-90 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- El Centro Chicano - Budget and Planning Committee 1987-88 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- El Centro Chicano - Budget and Planning Committee 1986-87 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- El Centro Chicano - Budget and Planning Committee 1985-86 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- El Centro Chicano - Budget and Planning Committee 1984-85 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- El Centro Chicano - Budget and Planning Committee 1980-85 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- El Centro Chicano Board (Box 70, Folder 23)
- de Nechochea - Faculty Affirmative Action 1978-1980 (Box 70, Folder 24)
- de Nechochea - Graduate Studies and Research Office 1981-1990 (Box 70, Folder 25)
- de Nechochea - Hispanic Leadership 1991 (Box 70, Folder 26)
- de Nechochea - Humanities Center 1987 (Box 70, Folder 27)
- de Nechochea - Tinker Visiting Professor Committee 1980-1989 (Box 70, Folder 28)
- de Nechochea - Washington D.C. Academic Program Planning Committee 1985 (Box 70, Folder 29)
- de Nechochea - Washington D.C. Academic Program Planning Committee Reports 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 30)
- Western Culture Program Committee - Area One Requirement Task Force meetings, Agendas 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 31)
- Western Culture Program Committee - Area One Requirement Task Force Charge/Roster 1987 (Box 70, Folder 32)
- Western Culture Program Committee Correspondence 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 33)
- Western Culture Program Committee Reports, Summary (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Western Culture Program Committee Background Information, Clippings (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Directorio Chicano 1976-1983 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Directorio Chicano 1984-1985 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- de Nechochea - Americas Program (Box 71, Folder 5)
- de Nechochea - ASSU Lobby Office (Box 71, Folder 6)
- de Nechochea - Ballet Folklorico 1989 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- SCCR (Stanford Center for Chicano Research) Events 1982-1988 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- SCCR Planning Group (Box 71, Folder 9)
- SCCR Working Papers (Box 71, Folder 10)
- SCCR General 1980-1983 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- de Nechochea - Proposals 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Casa Zapata (Box 71, Folder 13)
- de Nechochea - Centennial Celebration - Mexico City Conference (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Chicano Faculty Seminar 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Chicano Faculty Seminar 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Chicano Faculty Seminar 86-1987 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- La Raza Staff Association 1978-1989 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- MEchA (El Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan) 1969-1983 (Box 71, Folder 19)
- MEchA 1983-1989 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- MEchA 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- MEchA 1989-1990 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Casa Zapata Mural (Box 71, Folder 23)
- Noticias de Estanford - Stanford Noticias Newsletter 1978-1985 (Box 71, Folder 24)
- Bacchetti - Talk to Western Deans of Students 1977 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Bacchetti - "In praise of Good Questions" speech 1976 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Bacchetti - National Association for Equal Educational Opportunities speech 1976 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Bacchetti - "Funding for Libraries" speech 1976 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Bacchetti - NACUBO speech 1976 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Bacchetti - University Union of Japan speech 1975 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Bacchetti - "Student Influence in University Affairs" speech 1976 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Bacchetti - Pluralism Statement 1971 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Bacchetti - (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Bacchetti - Academic Planning Office 1969-1971 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Bacchetti - Decanal Indirect Cost Study 1988 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Bacchetti - Personnel Policies and Administration Survey 1982 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Bacchetti- Report On The More Effective Utilization of Resources 1972 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- UBPAC (University Budget Priorities Advisory Commission) Task Force I - Administration and Support Services 1975 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- UBPAC Task Force II - Student Services 1975 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- UBPAC Task Force III - Academic Calendar (Box 72, Folder 16)
- UBPAC Task Force IV - Faculty Development (Box 72, Folder 17)
- UBPAC Task Force V - Budget Equilibrium (Box 72, Folder 18)
- UBPAC Task Force VI - Professional Schools (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Advisory Group on the Bing Nursery School 1987-1989 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- The Future of the School of Education 1971 (Box 72, Folder 21)
- Physical Program for New Student Residences 1980 (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Transition Plan to Accessibility 1983 (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Lake Lagunita Report 1984 (Box 72, Folder 24)
- De Guerre Pools Accessibility Study 1983 (Box 72, Folder 25)
- New Undergraduate Residences 1979 (Box 72, Folder 26)
- Facility Project Development Process 1981 (Box 72, Folder 27)
- Circulation Plan 1988 (Box 72, Folder 28)
- Land Use Permit Modification Draft EIR 1985 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Biological Sciences Expansion Building Program Proposal 1985 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Biological Sciences Expansion Program 1986 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Biological Sciences Expansion EIR 1988 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Cost of Building at Stanford BOT Report 1979 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Project Management BOT Report 1979 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Facility Planning Process BOT Report 1976 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- NWC Project Management Plan 1985 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Advanced Materials Research Bldg Program 1987 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Green Earth Sciences Program Report v. I and II (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Marguerite Transit Study 1982 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Structural Evaluation of the Knoll phase I and II 1983 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Medical Center Regional Planning Report 1986 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Land Permit Modification Draft EIR 1986 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Structural Evaluation Old Chemistry 1984 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- NWC Surge Space Study 1984 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1976-1981 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Facilities Survey Phase II Planned Maintenance 1982 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Facilities Summary of Building Occupants 1989 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Organic Chemistry Remodel 1986 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- School of Medicine - Clinical Sciences Program Master Plan 1988 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- Cable Television 1982-1983 (Box 73, Folder 22)
- Information Technology - Database Management/Networking (Box 73, Folder 23)
- Survey of Institutes, Centers, Laboratories (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Overseas Studies Programs 1982 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- "What Seniors are Saying" Report 1989 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Conference for Privately Supported Libraries - Managing Under Austerity 1976 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Professional Opportunities Program CPPC 1982 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Compendium of Data and Information 1991 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Fraternities and Sororities at SU Policy Review 1983 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Statistical Reports on Composition of Faculty 1980 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Analysis of Faculty Appointment, Promotion, and Retirement 1973 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Statistical Study of the Curriculum 1987-1988 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- QSP Team on Work Simplification 1987 (Box 74, Folder 11)